Herbert Halpert collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Herbert Halpert collection 1930-2004 1936-1955
AFC 2004/008
Halpert, Herbert, 1911-2000
approximately 27,812 items
80 containers
approximately 34 linear feet
approximately 26,876 sheets
174 sound discs (aluminum): analog; various sizes, 10 in., 12 in., 16 in.
138 sound discs (acetate): analog; 12 in.
227 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; various sizes
396 photographs: prints, black and white; various sizes
1 photograph: print, color; approximately 4 in. x 4 in.
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Multiformat materials primarily representing the documentation and analysis of the folklore of regions of New York, New Jersey (particularly the New Jersey Pinelands region), Kentucky, Pennsylvania, Indiana, and Alaska by folklorist Herbert Halpert from the 1930s to 1950s.
Provenance
Violetta M. Halpert; Donation; 2004.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Related Material
These collections are at the American Folklife Center, Library of Congress:
Herbert Halpert New York City collection (AFC 1938/002)
Herbert Halpert New York and Pennsylvania Recordings (AFC 1938/010)
Herbert Halpert 1939 Southern States recording expedition (AFC 1939/005)
Herbert Halpert collection of Kentucky folk music (AFC 1950/005)
Herbert Halpert interview conducted by Peggy Farber, 1978 November 17 (AFC 1979/024)
Violetta M. Halpert interview conducted by David A. Taylor (AFC 2003/058)
Herbert Halpert Folklore Collection, Archives and Special Collections, Memorial University Libraries, Memorial University of Newfoundland https://www.library.mun.ca/asc/specialcollections/collections/halpert/
Access and Restrictions
The Herbert Halpert collection is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Biographical Note
Herbert Halpert was born in New York City, August 23, 1911. He studied folklore and anthropology for his M.A. from Columbia University. During the New Deal he recorded extensive collections of folk music, songs, and tales in New York, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and across the South for the Federal Theatre Project, the Joint Committee on Folk Arts of the Works Projects Administration (WPA), and the Library of Congress. He received his Ph.D. from Indiana University in 1942. He founded the Memorial University of Newfoundland Folklore and Language Archive (MUNFLA), and taught at the University for many years. Halpert died December 29, 2000.
Scope and Content
Sound recordings, correspondence, indexes, manuscripts, research notes, music transcriptions, photographs and photographic negatives, newspaper clippings, student papers, ephemera and other materials primarily representing the documentation and analysis of the folklore of regions of New York; New Jersey, particularly the New Jersey Pinelands region; Kentucky; Pennsylvania; Indiana; and Alaska by folklorist Herbert Halpert from the 1930s to 1950s. Includes publications edited by Herbert Halpert issued by the National Service Bureau of the WPA Federal Theater Project in New York City. Topics of Halpert's research included folk songs, folk belief, tales, legends, customs, and folklife. Includes photographs of interviewees and landscapes from the 1930s.
Arrangement
The Herbert Halpert collection is organized in 5 series:
Series 1. Herbert Halpert's fieldwork
Series 2. Writings and conference papers
Series 3. Research and publicity
Series 4. Student research - Indiana
Series 5. Student research - Kentucky
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Bowden, Morner, 1883-1961; Halpert, Herbert, 1911-2000; Halpert, Herbert, 1911-2000--Correspondence.; Halpert, Herbert, 1911-2000--Ethnomusicological collections.; Halpert, Violetta M.; Trout, Allan M., 1903-1972
Organizations
Federal Theatre Project (New York, N.Y.)
Subjects
Folk music--United States.; Folk songs, English--United States.; Folklore--United States.; Folklorists--United States--Correspondence.; Tales--New Jersey--Pine Barrens.
Places
Alaska--Folklore.; Indiana--Folklore.; Middle Atlantic States--Folklore.; New Jersey--Folklore.; New York (State)--Folklore.; Southern States--Folklore.
Form/Genre
Correspondence.; Field notes.; Folk tales.; Interviews.; Oral histories.; Photographs.
Container List
- Series 1: Herbert Halpert's fieldwork
  Previous title: Folklore: narratives, informants, and field notes
  - Subseries 1: Alaska
    - Alaskan tales - preliminary bibliography, undated (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Alaska, Northwest Canada - field notes, related materials, and photos, 1944, Includes five black-and-white photos, each measuring 4 1/4 in. x 5 1/4 in. and smaller (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Alaska - Indian tales, 1944 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Alaska - nicknames, 1944 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - "The Alaskan Frontier," 1944-1945, undated (Box-folder 1/5)
      An unpublished article on Alaskan folklore by Herbert Halpert, with an accompanying explanatory note from Violetta Halpert.
    - Alaskan tales and anecdotes, 1944 (Box-folder 1/6)
      Collected by Herbert Halpert.
    - "Hell in Alaska" and notes on "Hell in Texas," 1910-1985, undated (Box-folder 1/7)
      Photocopies and notes. "Hell in Alaska" is a manuscript copy obtained in Nome by a local informant. "Hell in Texas" was the prototype.
  - Subseries 2: Indiana
    Folklore by nationality, motif, and other categories
    - Folk beliefs, 1936-1941, undated (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Folk beliefs (unfiled), 1940-1941, undated (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Rhymes, 1940, undated (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Games, 1930-1941, undated (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Folk customs, 1940-1941, undated (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Songs, 1940-1941, undated (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Local histories, 1941 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Composed verse, 1940 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Belief slips (unsorted), circa 1940-1941 (Box-folder 1/16)
      Original folder title: Indiana University reports (original file)
    - Kentucky folklore (Indiana University collection), circa 1940 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Polish folklore (Indiana University collection), undated (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Greek folklore (Indiana University collection), 1941 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Dutch folklore (Indiana University collection), 1941 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Newby manuscripts, June-July 1958 (Box-folder 1/21)
      "To be typed" (handwritten note on the original folder)
    - Legends, 1940-1941, undated (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Folktales, 1940-1941, undated (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Indiana manuscripts: informants/interviews, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - Subseries 3: Mid-Atlantic region
    - Sub-subseries 1: General materials
      - New Jersey Pines and New York State - folksong texts and fieldnotes, 1937-1941, undated (Box-folder 2/1)
        Materials found loose with the New Jersey and New York folders
      - New Jersey/New York recordings - contents, 1939 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - New York and Pennsylvania folksong texts (second set), undated (Box-folder 2/3)
      - New York and Pennsylvania folktales - tales up the Delaware/East Branch, undated (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Pennsylvania, New Jersey, and New York recordings made by Herbert Halpert, 1941 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Pennsylvania lists, undated (Box-folder 2/6)
        Contacts and addresses, fieldwork, and part of a roadmap for eastern Pennsylvania
      - Mrs. Fred Coddlington - Pennsylvania songs, 1938-1939, undated (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Sub-subseries 2: New Jersey and New York archival data cards - folksongs
      Cards (and sometimes slips of paper) measure about 5" x 8". Pennsylvania material is also included, even though the original label from the donor does not indicate it.
      - By singers - text only, no recordings, 1937, 1939 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Dubs (not transcribed), 1937, 1939 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Titles of songs (1/11), 1937-1939 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Titles of songs (2/11), 1937 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Titles of songs (3/11), 1937-1939 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Titles of songs (4/11), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Titles of songs (5/11), 1937-1938 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Titles of songs (6/11), 1937 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Titles of songs (7/11), 1937 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Titles of songs (8/11), 1937 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Titles of songs (9/11), 1936-1941 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Titles of songs (10/11), 1936-1938, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Titles of songs (11/11), 1936-1940, 1942 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Pennsylvania and New York recordings (1/2), 1937-1939 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Pennsylvania and New York recordings (2/2), 1936-1940 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Singers, 1937 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Singers, 1938 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Singers, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Singers - members of the Edwards family (1/3), 1938, 1940, 1940 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Singers - members of the Edwards family (2/3), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Singers - members of the Edwards family (3/3), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Singers - members of the Wormuth family, 1941 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - By singer, from groups not transcribed (1/6), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - By singer, from groups not transcribed (2/6), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - By singer, from groups not transcribed (3/6), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - By singer, from groups not transcribed (4/6), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - By singer, from groups not transcribed (5/6), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - By singer, from groups not transcribed (6/6), 1938-1939, 1941 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Quotes and data from singers (from dictated texts, vol. 1), circa 1936-1941 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Quotes and data from singers (from dictated texts, vol. 2), 1936-1938, 1940 (Box-folder 6/2)
        The accompanying slip says "Copy data on Wainwright song" but this does not seem to match the folder contents. The current folder title was assigned by the archivist.
      - Singers' comments, 1936-1940 (Box-folder 6/3)
        Excerpted from dictated texts, vol. 3
      - Data from the title list of records, 1938 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Texts only, for book - music not recorded, 1936-1942, undated (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Texts only (New Jersey) - no recording or tune made, 1936-1942, undated (Box-folder 6/6)
        Arranged alphabetically by singer
      - New Jersey, on record (1/2), 1937 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - New Jersey, on record (2/2), 1937 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - New Jersey, on record (no dub), 1938 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Excerpts from New Jersey texts (Dictated Texts, vol. 2), 1937-1940 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Dubs (not transcribed) for 1st book, 1937, 1939 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - On records, 1941 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - New Jersey - music transcribed, 1937 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - New Jersey - music transcribed, 1938 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - New Jersey - music transcribed, 1939 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Music transcribed by Pol., 1937 (Box-folder 7/8)
        Noted on the documentation: "H has no copy."
      - Music transcribed by Pol., 1938 (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Music transcribed by Pol., 1939 (Box-folder 7/10)
      - New Jersey - music transcribed and checked by Bayard, 1937 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - New Jersey - dubs - music not transcribed, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - New Jersey - dubs - music not transcribed, 1939 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Texts with no music - no dub, 1939 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Sub-subseries 3: New Jersey and New York folksong index - titles and first lines
      - Index cards (Box 8)
        3 in. x 5 in. handwritten index cards.
  - Subseries 4: New Jersey
    - New Jersey folklore: narratives, informants, field notes, etc., undated (Box-folder 9/1)
      Photocopied cover page
    - List of tales and legends told by each informant, undated (Box-folder 9/2)
    - New Jersey maps and time tables, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 9/3)
      Used by Herbert Halpert on his collecting trips. Two of the maps are in delicate condition.
    - Interviews - New Jersey informants, A-K (work set), 1938-1940 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Interviews - New Jersey informants, K-Z (work set), 1938-1941 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - New Jersey field notes - informant information/contacts, etc., 1940, undated (Box-folder 9/6)
      Some pages are delicate
    - New Jersey field notes, 1951 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - New Jersey field work - Child ballad finding list and questions, 1936 or after (Box-folder 9/8)
    - New Jersey - field notes, letters, texts, and miscellaneous notes, 1937-1939, undated (Box-folder 9/9)
    - New Jersey Pines - research data (1/2), 1937-1941, undated (Box-folder 9/10)
    - New Jersey Pines - research data (2/2), 1937-1941, undated (Box-folder 9/11)
    - New Jersey texts - legends - Giberson and the devil (edited set), 1940-1942, 1946 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - New Jersey texts - legends - Munyhun - wizard of the Pines, 1940-1951, undated (Box-folder 10/1)
    - New Jersey texts - legends - devils, witches, and spirits (computer version), 1940-1951, undated (Box-folder 10/2)
    - New Jersey texts - strong man legends, 1940-1951, undated (Box-folder 10/3)
    - New Jersey texts - tales - fools and simpletons, 1940-1942, 1946 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - New Jersey texts - tales - surprising answers and retorts, 1940-1951, undated (Box-folder 10/5)
    - New Jersey texts - tales - tricksters and clever fellows, 1939-1941, undated (Box-folder 10/6)
    - New Jersey texts - tales - frightened by the supernatural, 1940-1955, undated (Box-folder 10/7)
    - New Jersey folklore/folklife collected from Stacy Bozarth, George Leek, and Rodney Koster, 1951 (Box-folder 10/8)
      Miscellaneous folklore collected from Stacy Bozarth, George Leek, and Rodney Koster.
    - New Jersey superstitions from storytellers and singers (set 2), 1940-1941 (Box-folder 10/9)
      From storytellers and singers
    - New Jersey riddles (set 2), 1940-1951, undated (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Charles Grant interviews (1/2), 1938-1941 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Charles Grant interviews (2/2), 1938-1941 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Charles Grant interviews, 1946 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Charles Grant interviews (photocopies) (1/2), 1938-1940 (Box-folder 11/1)
      According to a note written on the original folder, the originals (typescipts) are in separate folders
    - Charles Grant interviews (photocopies) (2/2), 1940-1942, 1946 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Folktale miscellany - tales - Clinton, New Jersey, 1946 (Box-folder 11/3)
      Halpert notes on the original folder: "not from Pines."
    - Folk songs other than New Jersey - Halpert collectanea - manuscripts and transcripts, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Record title list - New Jersey, 1937 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - New Jersey record lists, undated (Box-folder 11/6)
      By record number; by categories and titles. Includes drafts of letters to transcriber.
    - Title list of recordings made by Herbert Halpert, 1938 (Box-folder 11/7)
      Areas covered include New York, Pennsylvania, and New Jersey
    - New Jersey local (or localized) songs - list, circa 1930s-1940s (Box-folder 11/8)
      Photocopy (dated 1995) of older documents
    - New Jersey - locally made-up songs, 1940-1941, undated (Box-folder 11/9)
    - New Jersey field research on local disaster songs, 1939-1940, undated (Box-folder 11/10)
    - New Jersey - songs from children's lore, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - New Jersey songs - Ivins Grant manuscripts, undated (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Folk songs referred to in informant interviews - New Jersey, undated (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Background for New Jersey local songs and murder ballads, etc., undated (Box-folder 11/14)
      Transcripts by Herbert Halpert from contemporary printed material
    - New Jersey songs - local and miscellaneous, April 1995 (Box-folder 11/15)
      Photocopied in April 1995
    - New Jersey folksong texts (set 2, binder 1 of 2), 1936-1938, undated (Box-folder 11/16)
    - New Jersey folksong texts (set 2, binder 2 of 2), 1936-1938, undated (Box-folder 12/1)
    - New Jersey folksong texts (set 3, binder 1 of 2), 1936-1938, undated (Box-folder 12/2)
    - New Jersey folksong texts (set 3, binder 2 of 2), 1936-1938, undated (Box-folder 12/3)
    - New Jersey song texts, 1937-1938, 1952, undated (Box-folder 12/4)
      Handwritten on the original folder: "HH work file"
    - New Jersey song texts - no recordings, 1937-1939, undated (Box-folder 13/1)
    - New Jersey song texts, 1937 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - New Jersey song texts, 1938 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - New Jersey song texts, 1939 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - New Jersey folksong texts from recordings (1/2), 1937 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - New Jersey folksong texts from recordings (2/3), 1937 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - New Jersey folksong texts from recordings (3/3), 1937 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - New Jersey folksong texts (1/3), 1937-1939 (Box-folder 13/8)
      No recordings for this group.
    - New Jersey folksong texts (2/3), 1937-1939 (Box-folder 13/9)
      See the note for Box-Folder 13/8.
    - New Jersey folksong texts (3/3), 1937-1939 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - New Jersey folksong texts from recordings (1/3), 1938-1939 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - New Jersey folksong texts from recordings (2/3), 1938-1939 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - New Jersey folksong texts from recordings (3/3), 1938-1939 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Subseries 5: New York
    - Frank Edwards - Livingston Manor, New York - song texts, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - "Little George" Edwards - New York song texts - second set, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - "Little George" Edwards - New York song texts - third set, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 14/7)
      Includes an 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white photo of George Edwards (in the photo at left) and an unidentified man.
    - Jim Edwards - New York - original manuscript, undated (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Jim Edwards - New York song texts - second set, 1938 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Jim Edwards - Livingston Manor, New York, 1938 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Reuben Edwards - New York - song texts, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Edwards family - New York - field notes, undated (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Mrs. Elizabeth Misner - New York, 1938, undated (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Martin Montonyea - New York - song texts, 1938-1939, undated (Box-folder 15/5)
    - O'Dell (Lafe, Ralph, Marcus, and Preston) - New York, 1938, undated (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Charles Seeley - New York, 1938, undated, Includes 1 photographic print; 8 in. x 10 in. (Box-folder 15/7)
      Photo depicts George Edwards (at left) and Charles Seeley. See Box-Folder 78/6 for similar images.
    - George Swartwout - East Branch, New York, 1940 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Mrs. Minnie Ward - New York, 1938-1939, undated (Box-folder 15/9)
    - George Wood - Walton, New York, 1939 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - New York - lists, 1941, undated (Box-folder 15/11)
    - New York trip notes, 1946 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - New York interviews, 1941 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - New York interviews (set 2), 1938, 1941 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - New York interviews (set 3), 1938-1939 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - New York interviews, 1946 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - New York - miscellaneous letters, notes, etc., 1937-1939, 1941, undated (Box-folder 15/17)
    - New York songs (sets 2 and 3), 1941 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Southern New York - Ramapo, Sloatsburg, Tuxedo, 1938, undated (Box-folder 15/19)
    - New York City - children's rhymes grouped by classification, 1918-1931, undated (Box-folder 15/20)
      Made by Halpert during the 1930s and used as his M.A. thesis at Columbia. According to a note on the divider card preceding the folder, this material is not the same set as that in which the Federal Writers Project was involved.
    - New York City - children's rhymes, 1939-1940, undated (Box-folder 16/1)
      See the note for Box-Folder 15/20.
    - New York City - children's games/rhymes, 1940 (Box-folder 16/2)
      See the note for Box-Folder 15/20. The contents are described on the original folder as "Individual collectors (unique set - no duplicates found."
    - Tall tales on the East Branch, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Boney Quillan - New York's Tyll Eulenspiegel, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Paul Bunyan Back East, 1941, 1949, 1949 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Subseries 6: Southern recording trip and hillbilly records
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Ruth Saunders (Austin Harmon's daughter), 1978, Includes 1 photographic print (Kodak Land camera image): color; approx. 4 in. x 4 in. (Box-folder 16/6)
      Photo of Austin Harmon was taken in December 1977 when he was 77 years old.
    - Southern recording trip - information on contacts, informants, etc., 1939 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Virginia texts and interviews, 1939 (Box-folder 16/8)
      Texts from the Emory Hamilton collection and information on singers recorded by Herbert Halpert on the Southern recording trip
    - Hillbilly songs and records, 1936-1938, 1950, 1962, 1950, 1962 (Box-folder 16/9)
      Drafts of two unpublished papers and correspondence (1937-38) with The American Scholar regarding a projected article
    - Hillbilly songs on records - interviews with producers, circa 1936 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Hillbilly records from commercial catalogs - lists, circa 1936 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Subseries 7: Folklore from various locations
    - Manchester, New Hampshire - folktales and miscellaneous, 1945 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - New Hampshire folktales, 1945 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - South Carolina folktales, 1947 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Ohio folktales, 1947 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Carlinville (Illinois) folklore, May 1959 (Box-folder 17/4)
      From Warren S. Walker
    - Folklore of sports (Illinois manuscript), undated (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Arkansas folklore, Fall 1960 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Folktales and songs, 1951, 1996 (Box-folder 17/7)
      From Mrs. Charles G. Woodbury, Washington, D.C.
    - Songs and stories, 1961 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Subseries 8: Photographic materials
    The photographic materials are listed in approximately the order in which they are housed within each folder. This series was processed by Carl Fleischhauer. Photo titles/captions were developed by Carl Fleischhauer and Marcia Segal, based on available information. Three photos are historic in nature, and believed to have been provided to Halpert by the informants. All others are the result of Halpert's own fieldwork.
    - Photographs provided by informants and their families (Box-folder 77/11)
      - Charles Grant, 1 photograph: print (from a copy negative), black and white; 7 in. x 5 in.
      - Samuel Giberson, 1 photograph: print (from a copy negative), black and white; 8 in. x 5 in.
      - Mrs. Ella M. Francis, 1946, 1 photograph: print (from the original negative), black and white; 5 in. x 4 in.
    - Charles Bozarth (Box-folder 77/12)
      - Charles Bozarth, Tabernacle, NJ, circa 1938, 4 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
    - Stacy Bozarth (Box-folder 77/13)
      - Stacy Bozarth, Buddtown, NJ, circa 1938, 5 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 5 in. or smaller
        One photo shows Stacy with a young girl.
    - Photographs from negative sleeves (1/3) (Box-folder 77/14)
      All photos were taken in New Jersey.
      - Mrs. Julaney Stevenson, of Retreat, NJ; photographed at Mt. Holly, NJ, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - John Webb, Pleasant Grove, near Whiting, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller